https://www.tvps.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.
Note, the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.
We respect your privacy here at Executive Communication Systems. We will never sell or share any of your personal information. By agreeing to our site terms you are permitting us to use your email address for email marketing purposes. If you would prefer we not use your email address for email marketing purposes please contact us at sales@tvps.com notifying us of your intentions.
The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.
Executive Communication Systems uses Google AdWords Remarketing to advertise TVPS.com on websites across the Internet, specifically on the Google Content Network (GCN). AdWords remarketing may display relevant ads and special offers tailored to you based on prior visits to TVPS.com by placing a cookie on your machine. We respect your personal privacy and do not collect any personally identifiable information about you.   The cookie is used to say “This person visited this page, so show them ads relating to that page.” Google AdWords Remarketing allows us to tailor our marketing to better suit your needs and only display ads that are relevant to you.
You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Preferences page.
www.google.com/ads/preferences
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:
By E-Mail: sales@tvps.com
By Phone: (800)/(805) 644-9525
We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
